{"1": {"question": "What is the chamber music for strings set work?", "correct": "1st movement from the String Quartet in G Major K.387 'Spring'", "incorrect": ["1st movement from the String Quartet in G Major K.378 'Summer'", "1st movement from the String Quintet in G Major K.387 'Spring'", "1st movement from the String Quartet in G Minor K.378 'Autumn'"]}, "2": {"question": "Who wrote the chamber music for strings set work?", "correct": "Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart", "incorrect": ["Schubert", "Bach", "Beethoven"]}, "3": {"question": "What is the form of the Mozart first movement?", "correct": "Sonata form", "incorrect": ["Binary form", "Ternary form", "Rondo form"]}, "4": {"question": "What is the instrumentation of the Mozart first movement?", "correct": "2 violins, 1 viola, 1 cello", "incorrect": ["1 violin, 1 viola, 1 cello, 1 double bass", "3 violins, 1 viola", "2 violins, 2 violas"]}, "5": {"question": "How many movements are in the full piece of the Mozart?", "correct": "Four", "incorrect": ["Three", "Five", "Ten"]}, "6": {"question": "What key is the first movement in for the Mozart first movement?", "correct": "G major", "incorrect": ["D major", "G minor", "C major"]}, "7": {"question": "Briefly describe the phrasing in the Mozart first movement.", "correct": "The phrases are short and balanced (andecedent and consequent, or question and answer)", "incorrect": ["The phrases are long and smooth. Each phrase brings in a new idea.", "The phrases are unbalanced.", "The phrasing varies greatly, so there is no real way to define it."]}, "8": {"question": "Which of the following is NOT a compositional technique found in the Mozart first movement?", "correct": "Diatonic melodies", "incorrect": ["Recurring rhythmic motifs", "Imitation", "Chromaticism"]}, "9": {"question": "What is a string quartet?", "correct": "A genre of chamber music written for four string instruments", "incorrect": ["A genre of Baroque music written for four string instruments", "A subgenre of K-pop inspired by BTS written for four string instruments", "A genre of Classical music written for four orchestral instruments"]}, "10": {"question": "What separates mid-eighteenth century string quartets from Baroque forms?", "correct": "The lack of a basso continuo part", "incorrect": ["The lack of a second violin part", "The featuring of Jungkook", "Six movements in a quartet"]}, "11": {"question": "What kind of people did the string quartet appeal to?", "correct": "Eighteenth-century upper classes", "incorrect": ["Eighteenth-century working classes", "Nineteenth century upper classes", "BTS fangirls"]}, "12": {"question": "The string quartet was a ready form of private entertainment for whom?", "correct": "Wealthy individuals and families", "incorrect": ["Working-class individuals and families", "Bangtan Sonyeondan", "A large audience"]}, "13": {"question": "Why did composers manipulate conventions of string quartet form for their audiences?", "correct": "Because audiences for quartets (commonly upper classes) enjoyed musical literacy and were educated on the form, so manipulating conventions surprised and delighted them.", "incorrect": ["Because President Namjoon asked them to", "Because audiences for quartets (commonly upper and middle classes) enjoyed hearing the slight tweaks in convention, as it made it much more interesting for them to listen to.", "Because audiences for quartets (commonly upper classes) did not enjoy hearing differences from convention, and the composers liked to annoy them."]}, "14": {"question": "How many string quartets are in the complete set of the Mozart?", "correct": "Six", "incorrect": ["Ten", "Five", "Four", "24?"]}, "15": {"question": "Who did Mozart dedicate the set of string quartets to?", "correct": "Haydn", "incorrect": ["Yoongi", "Purcell", "Bach"]}, "16": {"question": "Which of Haydn's quartets inspired Mozart to write his Haydn Quartets?", "correct": "Haydn's Op.33 set, which Mozart studied closely", "incorrect": ["Haydn's Op.44 set, which Mozart studied closely", "Haydn's Op.22 set, which Mozart studied closely", "Haydn's Op.55 set dedicated to Seokjin"]}, "17": {"question": "When did Haydn hear the quartets that Mozart dedicated to him?", "correct": "1785", "incorrect": ["1995", "1795", "1775"]}, "18": {"question": "What did Haydn say to the father Leopold when he was visiting from Salzburg?", "correct": "Before God, as an honest man, I tell you that your son is the greatest composer known to me either in person or by name. He has taste, and, what is more, the profound knowledge of composition.'", "incorrect": ["BTS is the greatest band ever to form. Their music is wonderfully splendid and your son Wolfgang is quite a horrible composer compared to them.'", "I very much dislike the quartets that your son wrote in my name. They do not reflect my compositions at all. Rather, they are written much more in your son's style than mine.'", "Before God, as an honest man, your son will continue to be the great composer that he is and always has been. His quartets profoundly reflect mine with his own tasteful additions.'"]}, "19": {"question": "What is the Italian term used to indicate bowing on or near the bridge?", "correct": "Sul ponticello", "incorrect": ["Pizzicato", "Sul pontiv√©lla", "Bangtanio amazingo"]}, "20": {"question": "How many sections of violins are usually found in the symphony orchestra?", "correct": "Two", "incorrect": ["Three", "Four", "One"]}, "21": {"question": "Which of the following is NOT a way the Mozart is typical of the time period?", "correct": "Plays with formal conventions and expectations", "incorrect": ["Written in sonata form", "Uses Classical chamber music compositional techniques", "Development is in a related key"]}, "22": {"question": "What are the four movements of the complete Mozart?", "correct": "Fast movement, slow movement, minuet and trio, fast finale", "incorrect": ["Slow movement, minuet and trio, fast movement, fast finale", "There are three movements", "Minuet and trio, slow movement, fast movement, moderate finale"]}, "23": {"question": "Which is one of the expressive possibilities that the string quartet presented composers with?", "correct": "Greater subtleties than large-scale instrumental genres e.g. symphonies and concertos", "incorrect": ["Increased possibilities for tonal complexity, compared to large-scale instrumental genres", "Greater opportunities to feature J-Hope's rapping skills", "Less reliance on terrace dynamics, compared to solo works"]}, "24": {"question": "What is sonata form?", "correct": "A large-scale instrumental form consisting of three main sections: exposition, development and recapitulation.", "incorrect": ["A large-scale instrumental form consisting of three main sections: A, B, and A.", "A large-scale instrumental form consisting of two main sections: A and B.", "A large-scale instrumental form consisting of indefinite sections, in the order of A, B, A, C, A, D, A, E, et cetera."]}, "25": {"question": "Which of the following does the exposition NOT present?", "correct": "Tierce de Picardie", "incorrect": ["Thematic material", "Tonal contrast", "Modulating from the tonic to a related key (usually the dominant if the orgiinal key is major or the relative major if the original key is minor)"]}, "26": {"question": "Which of the following was NOT a composer of string quartets?", "correct": "John Dowland", "incorrect": ["Carl Dittersdorf", "Ludwig van Beethoven", "Johann Wanhal"]}, "27": {"question": "Mozart - What key does the piece modulate to for the development and what its relationship to the tonic key?", "correct": "D major, dominant", "incorrect": ["D major, subdominant", "E major, dominant", "B minor, relative minor"]}, "28": {"question": "Mozart - Which of the following is NOT part of the job of the development section?", "correct": "Repeat most of the exposition", "incorrect": ["Modulate through a range of keys", "Eventually go back to the tonic", "Work over' motifs and thematic material of the exposition e.g. through sequenes and dominant harmony."]}, "29": {"question": "Mozart - Which of the following is used in the B section (minor)?", "correct": "Augmented chords", "incorrect": ["Diatonic melody", "Slower tempo (langsam)", "Modulation"]}, "30": {"question": "Mozart - What does the 'K' in K. 387 mean?", "correct": "The catalogue of Mozart's works made by Ludwig von Kochel", "incorrect": ["The catalogue of Mozart's works made by Kai Huening", "The catalogue of Baroque works made by Ludwig von Kochel", "The catalogue of all classical works made by Ludwig von Kochel"]}, "31": {"question": "Mozart - What does the '387' in K. 387 mean?", "correct": "It is his 387th work, ordering chronologically", "incorrect": ["It is his 87th work in his 3rd decade", "It is his 387th work, ordering alphabetically", "It is his 378th work, ordering chronologically"]}, "32": {"question": "What does the term Allegro vivace assai mean?", "correct": "Fast and very lively", "incorrect": ["Very fast and very lively", "Very fast", "Brisk and lively"]}}